tweetsum.com 2009-03-02

# TweetSum :: Privacy

## Privacy

Date of Last Revision: Feburary 7, 2009

### Scope of This Policy

This privacy policy ("Policy") explains how personal information is collected, used and disclosed by TweetSum.com ("TweetSum", "we" or "us") with respect to your use of the Web site located at http://TweetSum.com (the "Site") and the services provided by TweetSum and accessed through the Site (the "Services").

### Changes to this Policy

We may revise and update this Policy at any time. We will provide notice that changes have been made by posting the revised Policy and updating the revision date at the top of the Policy. We encourage you to review the Policy whenever you visit the Site to make sure that you understand how your personal information is treated.

### Personal Information we Collect

We may collect various types of information about you including personal, demographic and aggregate data. "Personal information" means information that specifically identifies you such as your name, address, telephone number and email address. Personal information does not include aggregate information, which is data we collect about the use of the Site or the Services or categories of such users, unless it is linked with your other personal information. Aggregate data is used for a number of purposes such as to help us understand trends and user needs so that we can improve our products and services and is not subject to this Policy unless it is linked to your personal information. Personal information you voluntarily provide us may be collected in a number of ways through the Site and the Services, such as when you register for an account, create a profile or send us an email. We may also collect personal information when you or others post content, send an email or message to another user or participate in Workspaces or other interactive forums or features of the Site or the Services. In addition, from time to time we may collect personal information that you provide in connection with participation in surveys, sweepstakes, contests, games, promotional offers, and other activities on the Site. If you are a Workspace owner (the originator of a Workspace with the ability to invite users to join) we also will collect your credit card and billing information. Please see the section below Use of Cookies, IP Addresses and Web Beacons for a description of how some personal information also may be automatically collected through your use of the Site or the Services.

### Uses of Personal Information

In general, we use personal information that we collect to process your requests or transactions, to facilitate your use and our administration and operation of the Site and the Services, to provide you with information or services you request, to inform you about other information, events, promotions, products or services we think will be of interest to you, to learn more about and improve the Site and the Services and for the purpose for which information was provided. For example, we may use the information we collect to: 

  1. provide you with the services you request and to complete any transactions or enable the use of any features;
  2. send you a welcoming, account related or customer service email;
  3. contact you about our or a third party's services, products, activities, special events or offers;
  4. respond to your emails, submissions, comments, requests or complaints;
  5. process payments;
  6. request feedback and to enable us to develop, customize and improve the Site, the Services and new offerings; and
  7. notify contest winners.

### Sharing of Personal Information

TweetSum does not sell or rent personal information to third parties or share personal information with third parties except as described in this Policy, as it may be revised from time to time. We may share personal information with third parties when you request us to do so or otherwise give your consent. We may also share personal information with consultants, vendors and service providers ("Service Providers") who perform functions on our behalf. In addition, we may share your information with third parties if we have a good faith belief that the disclosure is necessary or appropriate to comply with law or legal process; to protect and defend the rights and property or personal safety of TweetSum, our customers or the public; to prevent and protect TweetSum and our users from fraudulent, abusive, unlawful or unauthorized use of the Site; or to otherwise enforce our rights and agreements. Your personal information also may be disclosed or transferred as part of, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition or in any other situation where personal information may be transferred as one of the business assets of TweetSum.

### Online Communities

The Site and Services include certain online communities and other interactive features, such as Workspaces, user profiles, forums and message boards. Please note that information you post or provide to public areas of the Site is publicly available and may be shared with other users. Other than your password, your registration information (i.e., name, email address, user ID and avatar photo, if selected) will be available to all members of any Workspace you join. The information you post in a Workspace may be available to other users who have joined that Workspace. You should always be cautious when giving out personal information to others in public online forums.

### Use of Cookies, IP Addresses and Web Beacons

The Site and some Services and advertisements on our Site, may contain "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data that is stored on your hard drive and records your preferences and other data about your visit to the Site. If we combine cookies with or link them to any personally identifiable information, we will treat this information as personal information; otherwise it is treated as and used in the aggregate. Clear gifs (also know as web bugs or web beacons) may also be used on the Site or in emails relating to the Site. Clear gifs are small, invisible graphic images that allow the collection of certain information and monitor user activity on the Site. We use cookies, clear gifs, frames, server log analysis and other technology to customize your experience with our Site and the Service. Most internet browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. If you block cookies, some portions of the Site and the Service may not function properly. We do not control cookies in third party ads, and we encourage you to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. We may also use a third party advertising company to display ads on the Site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this Site and other Web sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp.

### Protecting Personal Information

We strive to protect personal information while it is under our control. Your account information is accessible online only through the use of a password. To help protect the confidentiality of your personal information, you must keep your password confidential and not disclose it to any other person. You are responsible for all uses of the Site by any person using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been compromised or misused.

### Opting Out

If you do not wish to receive promotional email from TweetSum about our products and services, you may opt out at the time of registration or by logging in to your account settings online and updating your contact preferences. Please note, even if you opt out of receiving promotional email from TweetSum, you may still receive transactional and relationship emails, including messages relating to transactions or services you have specifically requested, responding to any email from you to us, notifying you of updates or changes to our policies and procedures, or which otherwise provide you with information we believe is important to users. Our systems require time to update, so your opt out requests may not update immediately.

### Special Notice Regarding Children

The Site and the Services are not designed for nor do we knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Any links from the Site to third party Web sites are provided for your convenience. Personal information you provide on the linked pages is provided directly to that third party and is not subject to this Policy. Please review the third party's privacy policy to better understand their privacy practices.

### Contact Information to Correct and Update Personal Information or Obtain Additional Information

If you have any questions, complaints or comments regarding our Policy or practices or you wish to verify, correct or delete any personal information we have collected, please contact us at "feedback" where the domain is "TweetSum" followed by a dot com. We will endeavor to respond to your inquiry or information request to the extent possible.
